19th-20th Century Architecture Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Latin America (Box 54)
  - Brazil (Box 54)
    - Rio de Janeiro [6 photographs] (Box 55)
      - Santo Dumont Airport [3 photographs] (Box 56)
      - Seaplane Station [6 photographs] (Box 56)
    - Sao Paolo [2 photographs] (Box 56)
      - Arnstein House [4 photographs] (Box 56)
      - Frontini House [5 photographs] (Box 56)
      - Library [2 photographs] (Box 56)
      - Sedes Sapientiae [2 photographs] (Box 56)
    - Salvador [4 photographs] (Box 56)
    - Sao Goncaluo (Box 56)
  - Chile (Box 56)
    - Santiago [22 photographs] (Box 56)
    - Valparaiso [7 photographs] (Box 56)
  - Cuba (Box 56)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 56)
    Xx Bonnet a l'Eveque, see Medium Size
    Xx Christophe's Palace at Milot, see Medium Size
    - Santo Domingo [2 photographs] (Box 56)
  - Guatemala (Box 57)
  - Mexico (Box 57)
    - Mexico City [8 photographs] (Box 57)
      - Churches [15 photographs] (Box 57)
      - Industrial Buildings [8 photographs] (Box 57)
      - Office Buildings [17 photographs] (Box 57)
      - Schools [24 photographs] (Box 57)
      - Theatres [4 photographs] (Box 58)
    - Puebla [2 photographs] (Box 58)
    - Queretaro [1 photograph] (Box 58)
  - Peru (Box 58)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 58)
  - Uraguay (Box 58)
    - Montevideo [2 photographs] (Box 58)
  - Venezuela (Box 58)
    - Caracas [6 photographs] (Box 58)